To sum up our discussion of activations it's obvious I think that
综上所述，我们对激活的讨论很明显，我认为
the activation tree depends on the runtime behavior of the program. So it depends on
激活树取决于程序的运行时行为。所以这取决于
the runtime value who's exactly which procedures are called and what the
谁是确切调用了哪些过程的运行时值，以及
activation tree turns out to be. Now, this was not illustrated in our examples but it
激活树原来是。现在，我们的示例中没有说明这一点，但是它
should be obvious that the activation tree can be different for different inputs. And
显然，对于不同的输入，激活树可以是不同的。和
so the programs I showed you didn't take input and so we didn't have, every time
所以我向你们展示的程序不接受输入，所以我们没有，每次
you run those programs we'll get the same activation tree, playing general if
你运行这些程序，我们会得到相同的激活树，如果
program takes input, it will execute differently and may call different
程序接受输入，它将以不同的方式执行，并且可能调用不同的
procedures and different orders. And finally here's perhaps the most important
程序和不同的命令。最后，这里可能是最重要的
point for an implementation point of view. Since activations are properly nested, we
从实现的角度来看。由于激活是正确嵌套的，因此我们
can use a stack to implement of detract the currently active activations. So,
可以使用堆栈来实现或减少当前活动的激活。所以,
let's see how we can use a stack to track activations. We'll use these examples that
让我们看看如何使用堆栈来跟踪激活。我们将使用这些示例
we looked at before. And what I'm going to do is I'm going to show the activation
我们之前看过了。我要做的是我要展示激活
tree over here on the left and I'm going to show the stack of currently executing
树在左边，我将显示当前正在执行的堆栈
activations on the right. So the stack is not gonna keep track of the entire
右侧的激活。所以堆栈不会记录整个
activation tree. It's only going to keep track of the activations that are
激活树。它只会跟踪
currently running so at each step of the program, the stack should contain all of
当前正在运行，因此在程序的每一步，堆栈都应该包含
the currently active or currently running activations. So, the tree we already saw
当前活动或当前运行的激活。那么我们已经看到的这棵树
have the build and we begin by executing main so that will be the root of the tree
有了构建，我们从执行main开始，这样它将成为树的根
And since the stack is supposed to have all of the currently running activations,
并且由于堆栈应该具有所有当前运行的激活，
the stack will have to have main on it. So it will begin with just the procedure main
堆栈上必须有Main。因此，它将从过程Main开始
And now main calls g And so g becomes a child of main And over here on the stack,
现在Main调用g，因此g成为Main的子级，在堆栈上，
we would push g on to the stack And then G returns and what that means is that, that
我们会将g推送到堆栈，然后G返回，这意味着，
G is no longer running and so G will get popped off the stack and then, the, the
G不再运行，因此G将从堆栈中弹出，然后，
main procedure calls F and so F will get pushed on to the stack And you can see
Main过程调用F，因此F将被推送到堆栈上，您可以看到
here that after G finishes we can pop it off and we can push on that and we
在这里，在G完成后，我们可以弹出它，我们可以推动它，我们
maintain the environment that we have a stack of the currently running
维护我们当前正在运行的堆栈的环境
activations. All right, then F is going to call G. I forgot to complete my tree here,
激活。好的，那么F会打电话给G。我忘了把我的树补齐了，
So main calls f and then f calls g. All right, So now the stack at this point is
所以main调用f，然后f调用g，好的，现在堆栈是
main f and g. And once g finishes running, it will be Popped off of the stack because
一旦g运行完毕，它将从堆栈中弹出，因为
it is no longer executing. And then f will finish, and f will also get popped off the
它不再执行。然后f会结束，f也会被弹出
stack and finally main will finish and main will also be popped off the stack.
堆栈，最后Main将完成，Main也将从堆栈中弹出。
And so that's the idea. So that is how we can use the stack. So essentially when a
这就是我们的想法。这就是我们使用堆栈的方式。所以基本上当一个
procedure is called we'll push an activation for that procedure on to the
过程时，我们将把该过程的激活推送到
stack. And when the procedure returns, we will pop that activation off the stack.
堆栈。当过程返回时，我们将从堆栈中弹出该激活。
And because activation lifetimes are properly nested this will work out. So, to
因为激活生命周期被适当地嵌套，所以这将是可行的。所以，为了
conclude our discussion of activations, let's return to the runtime organization
结束对激活的讨论，让我们返回到运行时组织
As you may recall. We have a block of memory that is allocated to the program
你可能还记得。我们有一个分配给程序的挡路内存
and the first portion of that block is occupied by the code for the program
挡路的第一部分被节目的代码占据
itself. And now in the rest of that memory that is allocated to the program, we are
它本身。现在，在分配给程序的内存的睡觉中，我们
going to have to restore the data that the program needs to execute and one of the
必须恢复程序需要执行的数据，并且其中一个
important structures that goes there is the stack of activations. So typically,
去那里的重要结构是激活堆栈。所以通常情况下，
this will start after the code area. And the stack would grow towards the other end
这将在代码区之后开始。堆栈就会朝另一端增长
of the memory space of the program and the stack will grow when procedures are called
程序的内存空间的大小，当调用过程时堆栈将会增长
and it will shrink when procedures return. And as we'll see, there are other things
当程序返回时，它会缩小。正如我们将看到的，还有其他一些事情
that go in this data area that we are going to be discussing in the upcoming videos.
我们将在接下来的视频中讨论这一数据区域。